Cauane Andrade

PORTUGUESE NATIVE, ENGLISH C2, GERMAN A1

Sao Jose dos Campos, SP, Brazil +55 12 99646-0749 cauane.emanuela@hotmail.com github.com/CauaneAndrade linkedin.com/in/CauaneAndrade

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a software developer with 3 years of experience using Python, JavaScript, SQL and GIS technologies as tools for government agencies and US electricity/natural gas holding companies.

I have knowledge in Docker containers, and using tools and processes that improves software engineering best practices like git, CI/CD pipelines, JIRA Suite, DevOps, etc.

I also have knowledge and experience working with location data in multiple tools/platforms such as GeoDjango, OpenLayers, and lately, ArcGIS.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Faculdade de Tecnologia de São Paulo Bachelor of Technology, System Analysis and Development

2018 - Jun 2022

FATEC is a Conceive Design Implement Operate (CDIO) collaborator. System Analysis and Development student.

Escola Técnica Estadual de São Paulo Marketing Technician, Marketing 2017 – 2018

ETEC is a government program aimed at training technical level professions.

Marketing Technician student.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Junior Software Engineer II TerraMagna

Feb 2022 - Present | Brazil

TerraMagna is a Agri/Fin Tech focused on managing credit risk for Agricultural lenders.

Development of applications using Satellite Image Processing, geographic data analysis and Artificial Intelligence.

Technologies: Python (Geo/Pandas), Flask, Rust (Tokio, Diesel ORM), Typescript, Google BigQuery, QGIS, Bazel, Unix/Linux.

Junior Software Engineer High Desert Spatial

Mar 2021 - Feb 2022 | Albuquerque, New Mexico, United States

High Desert Spatial is a global company that provides software development and GIS services to the utility industry.

Responsible for design and implementation of solutions using GIS technologies.

Technologies: ArcGIS products, ArcGIS API for Python/ArcPy, PowerShell, CA Workload Automation, FME Desktop, Oracle (standard and geographic), IBM Maximo, Windows.

Junior Software Developer Necto Systems

Mar 2019 - Mar 2021 | Sao Jose dos Campos, Sao Paulo, Brazil

Necto Systems is a company specialized in software development and consulting, focused on Data Science and GIS projects.

Responsible for implementing and testing solutions for government and government agencies using web technologies.

Technologies: Django/Django Rest Framework, unit test, Vue.Js, Docker/compose, Robot Framework, Bash, OpenLayers, GeoDjango, PostgreSQL/postgis, Unix/Linux.